{
  "name": "MTG",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "What does MTG stand for?",
      "answer": "Magic: The Gathering",
      "tags": [
        "Acronym",
        "Game",
        "Card Game"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary objective in MTG?",
      "answer": "To reduce your opponent's life total to zero.",
      "tags": [
        "Objective",
        "Gameplay",
        "Strategy"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the five colors of mana in MTG?",
      "answer": "White, Blue, Black, Red, Green",
      "tags": [
        "Mana",
        "Colors",
        "Gameplay"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a planeswalker in MTG?",
      "answer": "A powerful card type that represents allies who can assist you in the game.",
      "tags": [
        "Card Type",
        "Game Mechanics",
        "Strategy"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the term \"deck\" refer to in MTG?",
      "answer": "A collection of cards that a player uses to play the game.",
      "tags": [
        "Terminology",
        "Gameplay",
        "Strategy"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a token in MTG?",
      "answer": "A permanent created by spells or abilities that represents creatures or other types of permanents.",
      "tags": [
        "Gameplay",
        "Card Mechanics",
        "Tokens"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the phases of a turn in MTG?",
      "answer": "Untap, Upkeep, Draw, Main Phase 1, Combat, Main Phase 2, End Phase.",
      "tags": [
        "Turn Structure",
        "Gameplay",
        "Strategy"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a 'Tapping' card in MTG?",
      "answer": "The act of turning a card sideways to indicate that it has been used for the turn.",
      "tags": [
        "Gameplay",
        "Card Mechanics",
        "Tapping"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the significance of the ‘Legendary’ tag on a card?",
      "answer": "You can only have one copy of a legendary creature or planeswalker with the same name on the battlefield at a time.",
      "tags": [
        "Card Type",
        "Unique",
        "Gameplay"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'Lifegain' mean in MTG?",
      "answer": "Any action that increases a player's life total.",
      "tags": [
        "Gameplay",
        "Mechanic",
        "Strategy"
      ]
    }
  ]
}